"lang"
{
	"Language" "english"
	"Tokens"
		{
		"TIBS.pt_1"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: Hello, and welcome to the Aperture Science computer-aided enrichment center."
		"TIBS.pt_2"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: Due to subjects getting anxious, we have removed waiting to get rid of this human emotion."
		"TIBS.pt_3"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: Please place the Weighted Storage Cube on the Fifteen Hundred Megawatt Aperture Science Heavy Duty Super-Colliding Super Button."
		"TIBS.pt_4"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: As our previous statement suggested, we have removed waiting again to improve testing scores."		
		"TIBS.pt_5"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: Please go obtain the Aperture Science Handheld Portal Device to continue testing."		
		"TIBS.pt_6"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: It seems the Aperture Science Handheld Portal Device Stand has malfunctioned."	
		"TIBS.pt_7"	"<clr:243,95,0>TIBS: Monotone: Where are you going?	Human like: Where are you going?"
		"Fletcher_core.pt_1"	"<clr:169,169,169>Core: Quick! Over here!"
	}
}